

CONSTANTIN ANTOCHI

M, 41, Bucharest

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT:

+40755 041 747 constantin.antochi@gmail.com

Cactusului Street 10f, Building 2, Bragadiru

https://codepen.io/constantin-antochi
https://github.com/caphoto78
in/constantin-antochi-5328921/

PROFILE

I'm a career-changer who moved into programming two years ago.

I have finished the one year Link Academy "FrontEnd Javascript Developer" program and I've tested my skills sofar by gaining the Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures, Responsive Web Design and FrontEnd Libraries certifications from freecodecamp.com.

Because of my strong motivation and combining my artistic skills together with my fresh gained technical skills, I belive I can be the right person for a frontend developer or a web developer position.

MY PROJECTS

1. Fullstack responsive Todo List

Frontend Technologies used: Vue JS, VUEX, HTML, SCSS Backend Technologies used: Node.js, Express, Redis

2. Fullstack Nuxt Blog

Frontend Technologies used: NUXT, VUEX, HTML, CSS Backend Technologies used: Firebase

3. Vue Coaches App

Frontend Technologies used: Vue JS, VUEX, HTML, CSS Backend Technologie used: Firebase

Github source files

4. <u>FrontendMentor website</u> HTML, SCSS, Javascript

5. Javascript Projects

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

FRONTEND DEVELOPER - FREELANCER 2019 to present

- Design and implement new user interface designs for applications using JavaScript, SASS, HTML, Vue and React.
- Implementing fluid responsive frameworks

OWNER & PHOTOGRAPHER

Antochi Photography | 2009 to present

 Principal photographer and coordinator of the other photographers according to each event

SOFT SKILLS

- Capacity to work under tight deadlines;
- Quick learner;
- Attention to the details;
- Capable to work on goals hard to achieve, nonstandard situations are motivational key points for me;
- Team player;
- Good task organizer;
- Empathic;
- Communication skills;
- Creative

MY GOALS

I would like my first five years in front-end development to be about building my skills and knowledge as well as actively participating in the community and in making it a better and more accessible place for everyone.

CONTACT:

+40755 041 747 constantin.antochi@gmail.com

Cactusului Street 10f, Building 2, Bragadiru

https://codepen.io/constantin-antochi

https://github.com/caphoto78

in/constantin-antochi-5328921/

PRODUCT DESIGN MANAGER

BitDefender | 2006 to 2011 (5 years)

- Production of advertising materials for the whole department like: promotional layouts, folders, folders, leaflets, boxes, banners, product manuals, triptychs or other types of prints.
- Graphics elements execution that are required for the website, in collaboration with the website responsible and design web responsible (animation banners, landing pages);
- Making the ads necessary to promote the product in the media, based on instructions set by the image manager.
- Supervising the entire production cycle, from basic concept to typographical execution
- Design of presentation stands for all company's presentation to national and international exhibitions

LEARNING:

- 2019 2020 LINK Academy Frontend Javascript Development.
- 2019 2020 Udemy, Pluralsight, FreeCodeCamp, Skillshare, LinkedIn Web Developement Courses (my LinkedIn profile for the certifications).

EDUCATION

- Technical University of Constructions Bucharest (Graduated: 2002)
- Administrative School and Services Group "O. Onicescu" Botosani, finance-accounting (Graduated in 1996)

SOFTWARE KNOWLEDGE

HTML5		Sass/Scss	
CSS/CSS3	1111111111111000	Less	1111111111111000
JavaScript		Vue JS	
Webpack		React JS	
Babel	•••••	jQuerry	
Node.js	•••••	Bootstrap	
Typescript		Git/GitHub	111111111111111111111111111111111111111
Photoshop	1111111111111111	Adobe XD	
Illustrator		NUXT.js	••••••
InDesign	111111111111111	Ajax/Axios	•••••

FOREIGN LANGUAGES:

• English (Proficient User)